<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Ukmac</title>
        <link>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Ukmac</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 21:42:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>First post</title>
    <link>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/mypost/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 21:42:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/mypost/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This is the first post
 Bullet Bullet 2  ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Second post</title>
    <link>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/second-post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 21:42:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/second-post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[More Obsidian testing Test Test 2 Another head Today I came across this article on MacStories in which Federico Vittici describes how he uses Working Copy and GitHub to manage his writing with iA Writer and Pretext.
While I have been testing Working Copy I have tried creating a synced folder with the local Obsidian app folders and also with the Obsidians folder in iCloud. Both seemed to work fine but I was a bit unsure whether syncing with iCloud was recommended and hadn’t found any articles to confirm this was something you should do (in the past this sort of approach would have been a recipe for duplicated files and other odd issues).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Daily Post - 28/08/21</title>
    <link>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/2021-08-28-daily-post/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/2021-08-28-daily-post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[More Obsidian testing Today I came across this article on MacStories in which Federico Vittici describes how he uses Working Copy and GitHub to manage his writing with iA Writer and Pretext.
While I have been testing Working Copy I have tried creating a synced folder with the local Obsidian app folders and also with the Obsidians folder in iCloud. Both seemed to work fine but I was a bit unsure whether syncing with iCloud was recommended and hadn’t found any articles to confirm this was something you should do (in the past this sort of approach would have been a recipe for duplicated files and other odd issues).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>TextExpander Alternatives for Disgruntled Smile Customers</title>
    <link>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/2016-04-07-textexpander-alternatives-disgruntled-smile-customers/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://ukmac.net/ukmac2.github.io/posts/2016-04-07-textexpander-alternatives-disgruntled-smile-customers/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Over the last couple of days there has been a lot written about the Smile Software decision to move to a subscription model for version 6 of TextExpandermore, their popular text snippet app for OS X and iOS. Most of the words have understandably been pretty negative with users feeling that the change is purely a money grab by Smile. Obviously the economics of making a niche product like TextExpander pay its way are not simple and I really don&rsquo;t know if the change was actually an unavoidable option, but regardless of the reasons behind the decision it is fairly clear that a fair number of Smiles previous customers will be thinking twice about the upgrade and looking at alternative options.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
